Anthony Silva

Recent college graduate with 4 years of experience working on applications, forms and databases. Experience includes JavaScript based languages such as React, React Native, and Typescript. Highly motivated and ready to take on responsibilities to meet team goals with reliable performance. Team-oriented and hardworking with good verbal and written communication skills. GitHub: anthonysilva98



Contact

Address

Modesto, CA 95350

E-mail

anthonyssiva98@gmail.com



React-Native

Cloud Services (Google Firebase, GitHub)

SQL Familiarity

UML/Sequence Diagram

CSS

TypeScript

JavaScript

React

Express



Work History

2017-08 -Current

Carpenter

Central Valley Millworks, Oakdale, United States

- Plan and execute cabinet construction and instillation with proper tools and materials to maximize productivity.
- Plan projects by identifying necessary equipment, tools, and required assistance.
- Complete installations of building structures, trim, flooring and cabinetry.
- Fabricate custom furniture, shelving and cabinets and installed in specified locations.

2018-08 -2021-05

3D Printer Assistant

California State University Stanislaus, Turlock, CA

- Built, assembled, and gave suggestions on what machines should be acquired.
- Troubleshooting 3D printing issues, including replacing hardware and uploading software.



Education

2017-07 -20212

Bachelor of Science: Computer Science

California State University - Stanislaus - Turlock, CA



Accomplishments

• StanHacks 2019: First place project for building autonomous drone.

- HackFresno2019: First place project creating a nozzle that uses computer vision to detect objects to be manipulated.
- StanHacks 2 2020: Online website created during the pandemic to allow students to learn interactively without being in the classroom.
- Links to projects DevPost projects: https://devpost.com/anthonysilva98